[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Elisabeth Kubler-Ross"]}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", ":", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "How have you been coping?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "you", "been", "coping", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Well, you know, Elisabeth Kubler-Ross did this thing, this thing called the four stages of death and I actually -- of dying.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "Elisabeth", "Kubler-Ross", "did", "this", "thing", ",", "this", "thing", "called", "the", "four", "stages", "of", "death", "and", "I", "actually", "--", "of", "dying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 64, "question": "How have you been coping with this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "you", "been", "coping", "with", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "You know, I've said almost from the first moment that we learned that, \"We're devastated but we're not destroyed.\"", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "'ve", "said", "almost", "from", "the", "first", "moment", "that", "we", "learned", "that", ",", "``", "We", "'re", "devastated", "but", "we", "'re", "not", "destroyed", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "Kay, how had he been the night before?", "question_tokens": ["Kay", ",", "how", "had", "he", "been", "the", "night", "before", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "You know, he was -- it was actually one of the best weeks he's had in the long time.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "he", "was", "--", "it", "was", "actually", "one", "of", "the", "best", "weeks", "he", "'s", "had", "in", "the", "long", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "And how did you know he had a gun?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "did", "you", "know", "he", "had", "a", "gun", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "He had told me.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "had", "told", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Thursday", "April 4th"]}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "And what time was this?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "time", "was", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "That was late on Thursday, April 4th.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "late", "on", "Thursday", ",", "April", "4th", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "Did you go and try and see him?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "go", "and", "try", "and", "see", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "I didn't want to see what the possibility was.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "want", "to", "see", "what", "the", "possibility", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "EX", "JJ", "NN", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "What does that tell you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "that", "tell", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "Well it -- on a personal level, on a family level, on a government level, there'd be three different answers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "it", "--", "on", "a", "personal", "level", ",", "on", "a", "family", "level", ",", "on", "a", "government", "level", ",", "there", "'d", "be", "three", "different", "answers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "In the end, do you believe that he was correctly diagnosed, eventually?", "question_tokens": ["In", "the", "end", ",", "do", "you", "believe", "that", "he", "was", "correctly", "diagnosed", ",", "eventually", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "With something called?", "question_tokens": ["With", "something", "called", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "AY WARREN: Borderline personality disorder.", "answer_tokens": ["AY", "WARREN", ":", "Borderline", "personality", "disorder", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "And what is that?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Well, borderline personality disorder is a -- it's a pervasive attachment, if you will, to mood swings, suicide ideation.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "borderline", "personality", "disorder", "is", "a", "--", "it", "'s", "a", "pervasive", "attachment", ",", "if", "you", "will", ",", "to", "mood", "swings", ",", "suicide", "ideation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "How many times had he actually tried?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "had", "he", "actually", "tried", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "He had actually made two other attempts that were definite attempts plus all the attempts.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "had", "actually", "made", "two", "other", "attempts", "that", "were", "definite", "attempts", "plus", "all", "the", "attempts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "Before he'd taken an overdose or something?", "question_tokens": ["Before", "he", "'d", "taken", "an", "overdose", "or", "something", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "He had overdosed.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "had", "overdosed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matthew"]}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "``", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "And what did you say to him, Rick?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "did", "you", "say", "to", "him", ",", "Rick", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Well, in that situation, I said, \"Matthew, the reason why is there is a purpose, even in our pain.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "that", "situation", ",", "I", "said", ",", "``", "Matthew", ",", "the", "reason", "why", "is", "there", "is", "a", "purpose", ",", "even", "in", "our", "pain", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "Had he tried to do it legally?", "question_tokens": ["Had", "he", "tried", "to", "do", "it", "legally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "When did he finally get this gun?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "he", "finally", "get", "this", "gun", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "A month before he took his life.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "month", "before", "he", "took", "his", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "And do you know how he got it, who he got it from?", "question_tokens": ["And", "do", "you", "know", "how", "he", "got", "it", ",", "who", "he", "got", "it", "from", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "He told me that he -- he told me everything and he told me that he had found somebody finally on the internet who would sell it to him and it had to be super encrypted and it had to be, you know, this whole process and he begged me to help him because he couldn't figure out the process.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "told", "me", "that", "he", "--", "he", "told", "me", "everything", "and", "he", "told", "me", "that", "he", "had", "found", "somebody", "finally", "on", "the", "internet", "who", "would", "sell", "it", "to", "him", "and", "it", "had", "to", "be", "super", "encrypted", "and", "it", "had", "to", "be", ",", "you", "know", ",", "this", "whole", "process", "and", "he", "begged", "me", "to", "help", "him", "because", "he", "could", "n't", "figure", "out", "the", "process", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Do you know who that person is, Rick?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "who", "that", "person", "is", ",", "Rick", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Have no idea.", "answer_tokens": ["Have", "no", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "The police have never been able to find out?", "question_tokens": ["The", "police", "have", "never", "been", "able", "to", "find", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "And what -- and, Rick, have you been able to forgive this person?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "--", "and", ",", "Rick", ",", "have", "you", "been", "able", "to", "forgive", "this", "person", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", ":", "CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Oh yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Is there anything that can be done with that?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "anything", "that", "can", "be", "done", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "Is it affecting what you're going to be saying about this going forward?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "affecting", "what", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "be", "saying", "about", "this", "going", "forward", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "Well yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Kay, people say it's a second amendment right of every American to have guns, what do you say to them?", "question_tokens": ["Kay", ",", "people", "say", "it", "'s", "a", "second", "amendment", "right", "of", "every", "American", "to", "have", "guns", ",", "what", "do", "you", "say", "to", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Kay you only lasted a couple of minutes, because you found it's so difficult which is completely understandable, but for you Rick that moment when you walked out?", "question_tokens": ["Kay", "you", "only", "lasted", "a", "couple", "of", "minutes", ",", "because", "you", "found", "it", "'s", "so", "difficult", "which", "is", "completely", "understandable", ",", "but", "for", "you", "Rick", "that", "moment", "when", "you", "walked", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "I was overwhelmed by the love of our people.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "overwhelmed", "by", "the", "love", "of", "our", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick"]}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Kay, have you gone through any doubt about your faith?", "question_tokens": ["Kay", ",", "have", "you", "gone", "through", "any", "doubt", "about", "your", "faith", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "You know as Rick said it's not -- our faith is currently what's got us -- that foundation what's gotten us through and it's solid and strong but I have to tell you that, you know, before -- I have something I want to show you.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "as", "Rick", "said", "it", "'s", "not", "--", "our", "faith", "is", "currently", "what", "'s", "got", "us", "--", "that", "foundation", "what", "'s", "gotten", "us", "through", "and", "it", "'s", "solid", "and", "strong", "but", "I", "have", "to", "tell", "you", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "before", "--", "I", "have", "something", "I", "want", "to", "show", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Is there any sense of relief as a family that Matthew is now with God in heaven?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "any", "sense", "of", "relief", "as", "a", "family", "that", "Matthew", "is", "now", "with", "God", "in", "heaven", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matthew"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "Out of pain?", "question_tokens": ["Out", "of", "pain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "Yeah, if I didn't have that hope I would be in ultimate despair but we have built our lives, our faith, our family, our ministry on the belief that because of Jesus Christ and because of what he did on the cross for us we can have our past forgiven, we have a purpose for living, and we have a home in heaven that takes care of my past, my present, and my future.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "if", "I", "did", "n't", "have", "that", "hope", "I", "would", "be", "in", "ultimate", "despair", "but", "we", "have", "built", "our", "lives", ",", "our", "faith", ",", "our", "family", ",", "our", "ministry", "on", "the", "belief", "that", "because", "of", "Jesus", "Christ", "and", "because", "of", "what", "he", "did", "on", "the", "cross", "for", "us", "we", "can", "have", "our", "past", "forgiven", ",", "we", "have", "a", "purpose", "for", "living", ",", "and", "we", "have", "a", "home", "in", "heaven", "that", "takes", "care", "of", "my", "past", ",", "my", "present", ",", "and", "my", "future", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "There have been two strands I think that should be in particularly vicious in your case, one are these fake accounts set up supposedly on your behalf?", "question_tokens": ["There", "have", "been", "two", "strands", "I", "think", "that", "should", "be", "in", "particularly", "vicious", "in", "your", "case", ",", "one", "are", "these", "fake", "accounts", "set", "up", "supposedly", "on", "your", "behalf", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CD", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matthew"]}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "What is your reaction to it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Well, first Matthew wasn't gay but if it was we would have loved him unconditionally anyway.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "Matthew", "was", "n't", "gay", "but", "if", "it", "was", "we", "would", "have", "loved", "him", "unconditionally", "anyway", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "Do you have anything you think if only we had tried?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "anything", "you", "think", "if", "only", "we", "had", "tried", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "Of course that's part of grief.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "that", "'s", "part", "of", "grief", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "CD", "``", "WP", "IN", "''", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "WP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 587, "question": "What if we done that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "if", "we", "done", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "Rick, the one \"what if\" that springs to mind for me example if I was in your position and thank God I'm not, but if I had been as suppose the what if knowing he'd acquired an illegal gun...", "answer_tokens": ["Rick", ",", "the", "one", "``", "what", "if", "''", "that", "springs", "to", "mind", "for", "me", "example", "if", "I", "was", "in", "your", "position", "and", "thank", "God", "I", "'m", "not", ",", "but", "if", "I", "had", "been", "as", "suppose", "the", "what", "if", "knowing", "he", "'d", "acquired", "an", "illegal", "gun", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "... it could have made any difference?", "question_tokens": ["...", "it", "could", "have", "made", "any", "difference", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "Does it breaches the family members' right?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "breaches", "the", "family", "members", "'", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matthew"]}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "Let's get this Rick, have you questioned any stage whether you should have done more as Rick Warren, America's pastor about this issue of mental health before Matthew took his life?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "get", "this", "Rick", ",", "have", "you", "questioned", "any", "stage", "whether", "you", "should", "have", "done", "more", "as", "Rick", "Warren", ",", "America", "'s", "pastor", "about", "this", "issue", "of", "mental", "health", "before", "Matthew", "took", "his", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RBR", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "Piers, we've always known since Matthew has lived his entire life that one day we would be spokespeople for mental illness.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "we", "'ve", "always", "known", "since", "Matthew", "has", "lived", "his", "entire", "life", "that", "one", "day", "we", "would", "be", "spokespeople", "for", "mental", "illness", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick", "Rick Warren", "Matthew"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "How would you like him to be remembered Kay?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "like", "him", "to", "be", "remembered", "Kay", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "Oh, my funny, quirky, ridiculously, silly, deeply compassion.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "my", "funny", ",", "quirky", ",", "ridiculously", ",", "silly", ",", "deeply", "compassion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Matthew"], "PERSON": ["Kay"]}, "docId": "130917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "VBN", "NNS", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "CC", "DT", ":", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "Do you feel his -- he is here now?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "his", "--", "he", "is", "here", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "Well, I know that he's in heaven looking down on us and we have many loved ones there, my parents, Kay's mom and dad and the -- that presence of God is more important than the presence of Matthew in my life.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "know", "that", "he", "'s", "in", "heaven", "looking", "down", "on", "us", "and", "we", "have", "many", "loved", "ones", "there", ",", "my", "parents", ",", "Kay", "'s", "mom", "and", "dad", "and", "the", "--", "that", "presence", "of", "God", "is", "more", "important", "than", "the", "presence", "of", "Matthew", "in", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]